>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 所以他们只能走这么远。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So
they can only go so far.
他们可以告诉你我们在编译时能告诉你什么
They can tell you what we can
tell you at compile time, but
他们无法真正告诉你真实世界会发生什么
they can't really tell you anything about
what's gonna happen in the real world.
他们只希望这一切都不会咬你
They're just gonna hope that
none of that bites you.
>> Kyle Simpson: 以下是 TypeScript 和 Flow 的一些示例，以及
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So
some examples of TypeScript and Flow, and
这两个例子其实是一样的。
these examples are actually
identical between the two.
它们在这些情况下使用相同的语法。
They use identical syntax in these cases.
有几个细微的细微差别。
There are a few little
nuanced differences.
但我对这一准备工作的研究却非常吃惊
But I was actually remarkably surprised
in my research for this preparation how
类似的 " 类型脚本 " 和 " 流 " 是它们的外观。
similar TypeScript and Flow are in
terms of of what they look like.
我估计会有很多不同之处，也很少，好吗 ?
I expected a lot of differences and
there are very few, okay?
第一，如果你不做任何输入，都是 TypeScript 和
So number one, if you don't do any
typing at all, both TypeScript and
缺省情况下，流将执行某些注入。
Flow by default will do some inferencing.
所以他们在做静态的推论，这意味着我的意图是
So here they're doing a static types
inference, which means my intent that
他们猜的是我想要老师这个变量只能维持弦
they're guessing, is that I want teacher,
the variable to only ever hold strings.
当我尝试给它分配一些非字符串的时候
And when I later try to assign
it something non-string,
它会给我一个错误说你做了一个不该做的任务
it throws me an error, and says, you're
doing an assignment that you shouldn't do.
这是他们最好的猜测
That's their best guess.
有些人觉得在类型中最大的问题之一就是我们
Some people feel that one of the biggest
problems within types is that we
无意中将值分配给一个不是我们认为的类型的变量。
accidentally assign a value to a variable
that is not the type we thought.
对他们来说，静态类型是一个很大的交易。
And so for them,
static types are a big deal.
我跟你说在我 20 多年的时间里
I'm being honest with you when I
tell you that in my 20 plus years in
编码从来没有，一次不小心是我意外的结果
coding never once, not once has a bug
been as a result of me accidentally
将数字分配给用于保存字符串的变量，例如。
assigning a number to a variable that
used to hold a string, for example.
我是故意这么做的但从来没有意外发生过
I do that on purpose a lot, but never
once has that accidentally happened, and
是一只虫子的来源
been the source of a bug.
所以对我来说，这不是我所遇到的问题之一。
So for me, that's not one of
the problems that I have.
如果这是你的问题
If it is a problem that you have,
错误发生的原因是您重新分配了不正确的内容，这很有用。
where bugs come because you've reassigned
something incorrectly, this is helpful.
这是很久以来的其中一个特点
This is one of those features that,
for a long time,
我说我不需要这部分的 TypeScript。
I said I don't need that
part of TypeScript.
我不喜欢抱怨我分配变量的事
I don't like for it to complain to
me about what I assign variables,
cuz 我喜欢分配一个数字，然后再分配一个字符串。
cuz I like to be able to assign
a number and then later a string.
对我有帮助
That to me is helpful, so
我不喜欢这个部分，我觉得它解决了一个我没有的问题。
I didn't like this part, and I felt like
it was solving a problem I didn't have.
但这就是我们所说的静态类型
But that's what we refer
to as static types,
根据进入变量的值来推断变量的类型。
inferring that the variable has a type
based upon the value that goes into it.
JavaScript 变量没有类型，但是
JavaScript variables don't have types, but
如果你愿意的话我们就会有额外的要求
we're layering on this extra
requirement if you will, okay?
所以当我们不讨厌那种类型的时候
So that's when we don't
annotate the types, but
我们当然可以为这些类型烦恼
of course we can annotate the types.
我们可以说老师肯定是一个字符串。
We can say teacher is definitely a string.
我们会得到同样的错误，但在这里我们不能猜测错误。
We're gonna get basically the same error,
but here we're not guessing at the error.
我们真的是说我想让这件事只会保留弦子
We're literally saying I intended for
this thing to only ever hold strings, and
现在你想给它放点非弦的东西
now you're trying to put
something non-string to it.
在这两种情况下， TypeScript 和 Flow 会向我们抛出错误并指出，
In both cases TypeScript and
Flow are gonna throw us an error and say,
你会给你分配不该有的东西好吗
you're assigning something
you shouldn't have, okay?
好的
Great